Register of the Jan Karski Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1941-1997. (Box 12-13)
  - United States State Department. Documents related to Poland, 1943-1945 (Folder 13: 9)
  - Wajnryb, Mieczysław, The Economic and Social Importance of the Central Industrial District of Poland, 1938 (Folder 13: 10)
  - Warsaw Uprising, 1944
    - General, 1944 (Folder 13: 11)
    - Dispatches, Royal Air Force officer, August 13-September 28, 1944.; In English (Folder 13: 12)
    - Dispatches, Underground leadership, August 3-October 3, 1944; In English (Folder 13: 13)
    - Dispatches, Underground leadership, August 3-October 3, 1944; In Polish (Folder 13: 14)
    - German radio and press reports, 1944.; In Polish and English (Folder 13: 15)
    - Warsaw's Last Appeal to the Peoples of the World, 1944 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Wiesel, Elie. Introduction to Karski, 1944 (Folder 13: 17)
  - Zwiazki Ziem Wschodnich Rzeczypospolitej, 1943-1946
    - General, 1943-1946 (Folder 13: 18)
    - Bulletin, 1945-1946 (Folder 13: 19-20)
  - Zygielbojm, Szmul, 1997
    - Swięcicki, Marcin. Speech on occasion of unveiling of monument, 1997 (Folder 13: 21)
    - Theater play by Mieczysława Zawacz. Typescript, 1997 (Folder 13: 22)
- Printed Matter, 1939-1993. (Box 4-8, 13)
  Various published materials including clippings, brochures, digests, post-war émigré journals, pamphlets and posters.
  Arranged by physical form and title
  - Argentina, 1945 October-November (Folder 4: 1)
  - Aria z Kurantem by Jan Lechoń (Folder 4: 1)
  - Current News on the Lithuanian Situation, 1944 January-September (Folder 4: 2)
  - Current News on the Lithuanian Situation, 1944 October-1945 June (Folder 4: 3)
  - Democratic Postwar Reconstruction in Central Eastern Europe (Folder 4: 4)
  - Digest of the Polish Press - Overseas News Agency (ONA), 1942 October-1943 May (Folder 4: 5)
  - Digest of The Ukrainian Press - Overseas News Agency (ONA), 1942 October-1943 May (Folder 4: 6)
  - Dziennik Ustaw Rzeczypospolitej Polskiej, 1939 October-1942 March (Folder 4: 7)
  - Dziennik Żołnierza (Folder 5: 1)
  - Gazeta Żołnierza, 1945 November 20-21 (Folder 5: 1)
  - Glimpses of Polish Architecture by Roman Sołtyński (Folder 5: 1)
  - Głos Polski - Africa, 1945 October-November (Folder 5: 2)
  - Głos Polski - Hanover, 1945 July-November (Folder 5: 3)
  - Goniec Karpacki, 1945 (Folder 5: 4)
  - Human Events - "The Problem of the Baltic States" by K. R. Pusta (Folder 5: 5)
  - Information Bulletin, 1945 August-October (Folder 5: 5)
  - Jutro Polski (Poland of tomorrow - a Polish weekly,) 1945 August-November (Folder 5: 5)
  - Klub Polskich Ziem Zachodnich, 1944-1945 (Folder 5: 6)
  - Klucz do Piłsudskiego by Stanisław Mackiewicz (Folder 5: 7)
  - Książka Dla Wszystkich by Feliks Korniszewski (Folder 5: 7)
  - Latvia Under German Occupation 1941-1943 (Folder 5: 8)
  - The Libraries of Poland by Maria Danilewicz (Folder 5: 8)
  - Na Szlaku Kresowej, 1944 September-December (Folder 6: 1)
  - Na Szlaku Kresowej, 1945 February-November (Folder 6: 2)
  - Ochotniczka, 1945 October-December (Folder 6: 3)
  - Orzeł Biały, 1945 December 16 (Folder 6: 3)
  - Organizacja Bojowa Katorga - Rewolucja Rosyjska by Jan Kwapiński (Folder 6: 3)
  - Pismo Żołnierza, 1945 October-December (Folder 6: 4)
  - Podzwonne Za Kaprala Szczapę by Kazimierz Wierzyński (Folder 6: 4)
  - Polacy u Siebie by Zygmunt Nowakowski (Folder 6: 5)
  - Polak w Indiach, 1945 June-October (Folder 6: 6)
  - Poland Fights, 1945 September-October
  - Poland Here Is the Record by Ann Su Cardwell
  - Polish Digest, 1945 March-October (Folder 6: 7)
  - Polish Red Cross and Polish YMCA bulletins (Folder 6: 9)
  - Polska Walcząca, 1944 October 7, 1945 September-October (Folder 6: 10)
  - Promień, 1945 October-1946 March (Folder 7: 1)
  - Przedświt, 1941 June-July
  - Serwis dla Dzieci, 1945 (Folder 7: 2)
  - Skaut, 1945 March-April (Folder 7: 3)
  - Smocza 13 by Stefania Zahorska (Folder 7: 4)
  - Souvenirs de Staro-Bielsk by Joseph Czapski
  - Spadochron, 1945 October-November
  - Statistical Atlas of Poland by Edward Szturm De Sztrem (Folder 7: 5)
  - Stowarzyszenie Polskich Kombatantów Okręg - Szkocja, 1947 October-November
  - Światopol, 1944-1945, 1947 (Folder 7: 6)
  - Taran, 1945 October-December (Folder 7: 7)
  - "To the Members of Both Houses of Parliament" - Letter (Folder 7: 8)
  - Tygodnik Polski (a Polish weekly,), 1945 June-December (Folder 7: 8)
  - The Voice of Poland, 1945 June 17 (Folder 7: 9)
  - W Imię Boże, 1945 November-December (Folder 7: 9)
  - W Szpitalu Pod Dwoma Okupacjami by Marta Wańkowiczówna (Folder 7: 9)
  - What Poland Wants by Ignacy Matuszewski (Folder 7: 9)
  - Whitehall News, 1945 June 15 (Folder 7: 9)
  - Wiadomości, 1945 October-November (Folder 7: 9)
  - Wiadomości Kresowej, 1945 March-December (Folder 7: 10)
  - Żolnierz Polski - Żyd (Polish-Jewish soldier,) 1943 September 29 (Folder 7: 11)
  - Different speeches from Trenton, New Jersey, 1945 January 28 (Folder 7: 11)
  - Polish American Congress publications
    - Brochures
      - By-Laws of the Polish American Congress (Folder 8: 1)
      - Eastern Poland: Its Historical, Ethnographic, Economic, Political and Cultural Background (Folder 8: 1)
      - Foreign Policy of the United States (2 copies) (Folder 8: 1)
      - Keynote Address by Charles Rozmarek, 1944 May 28 (Folder 8: 1)
      - A Memorandum to the Senate of the United States On the Crimea Decisions Concerning Poland (Folder 8: 1)
      - Memorial of the Polish American Congress to Franklin Delano Roosevelt, President of the United States (Folder 8: 1)
      - Pięć Lat Straszliwych Cierpień i Walk Narodu Polskiego 1939-1944 (Folder 8: 1)
    - Bulletin, 1945 February-July (Folder 8: 2)
    - Leaflets, articles
      - Aims and Objectives of the Polish American Congress (Folder 8: 3)
      - Congressional Record - Appeal by the Polish-American Congress (2 copies) (Folder 8: 3)
      - Declaration of Polish American Congress, Inc. on Present Polish Situation (in English and Polish) (Folder 8: 3)
      - Memorandum Kongresu Polonii Amerykańskiej (memorandum of Polish American Congress) (Folder 8: 3)
      - A Memorandum to the Senate of the United States on the Crimea Decisions Concerning Poland (Folder 8: 3)
      - The Polish Constitution of the Third of May (Folder 8: 3)
      - Resolution of the Polish American Congress (Folder 8: 3)
      - Rozmarek Domaga się Sprawiedliwości dla Polski (Rozmarek appeals for justice for Poland) (Folder 8: 3)
      - Ustawy i Reguły Kongresu Polonii Amerykańskiej (laws and forms of the Polish American Congress) (Folder 8: 3)
      - The Voice of America (Folder 8: 3)
      - The United States, Poland and the Atlantic Charter, 1945 (Folder 8: 3)
        Includes excerpts from editorials printed in American newspapers
      - Who May and Should Participate in the Polish American Congress (Folder 8: 3)
      - Wzory Telegramów (suggestions on sending telegrams to Congressmen, the Department of State, etc.) (Folder 8: 3)
      - Z Działalności Zarządu Wykonawczego Kongresu Polonii Amerykańskiej (Polish American Congress Executive Committee activities) (Folder 8: 3)
    - Periodicals - Delegates Newsletter, 1944 December-1945 July (Folder 8: 4)
    - Protocols - Protokół Kongresu Polonii Amerykańskiej (Folder 8: 5)
    - Various published material (brochures, pamphlets, articles)
      - The Anglo-American Powers and India by Taraknath Das (Folder 8: 6)
      - Archiwum Polityczne (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Boundaries of Poland (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Chicago Conference on International Civil Aviation (Folder 8: 6)
      - Commemoration of Professor Malinowski (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Decline of European Culture and Its Reconstruction by Feliks Gross (Folder 8: 6)
      - Educational Reconstruction in Europe by Feliks Gross (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Fruits of Teheran by Isaac Don Levine (Folder 8: 6)
      - International Aspects of Adult Education by Feliks Gross (Folder 8: 6)
      - Manifest do Ludów Świata (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Nineteenth Century and After (Folder 8: 6)
      - Nowa Polska po Poczdamie (Folder 8: 6)
      - An Open Letter to the Newspapermen of America (Folder 8: 6)
      - Peace Planning for Central and Eastern Europe by Feliks Gross (Folder 8: 6)
      - Polish Constitution Day (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Polish Proletariat and Socialism by Feliks Gross (Folder 8: 6)
      - The Pre-War Unionization of Polish Workers by Władysław R. Malinowski (Folder 8: 6)
      - Przyszłość Demokratycznego Socjalizmu (Folder 8: 6)
      - Rozprawa Sądowa (Folder 8: 6)
    - Miscellaneous material
      - Information about the lecture by Jan Karski at Stanford University, 1995 March 6 (Folder 8: 7)
      - Audiocassettes, (may be sound recordings of the above lecture at Stanford) (Folder 8: 7)
      - Photocopies of notes to Colonel Antoine Daniel-Zdrojewski (Folder 8: 7)
  - Clippings, 1960-1993 (Folder 13: 23)
  - Posters, after 1945 (Folder 13: 24)
    Polish émigré printed in Great Britain about social and commemorative events
  - Various published materials, brochures, pamphlets, clippings, 1999-2000
    - Gabinet Prof. Jana Karskiego, Łodz, 1999 (Folder 13: 25)
    - Publications in honor of Jan Karski, 1997-2000 (Folder 13: 26)
    - Remember. To the Memory of Jan Karski the Righteous Gentile Whose Recent Death Jewry Mourns, undated (Folder 13: 27)
- Scrapbooks, 1943-2000. (Box 14-23)
  Scrapbooks with clippings, diplomas, flyers, press releases, interviews, letters of appreciation from prominent individuals.
  Arranged chronologically by Jan Karski
  - Vol. 1, 1943-1944 (Box 14)
  - Vol. 2, 1944-1945 (Box 14)
  - Vol. 3, 1945-1946 (Box 15)
  - Vol. 4, 1947-1958 (Box 15)
  - Vol. 5, 1957-1967 (Box 16)
  - Vol. 6, 1959-1980 (Box 16)
  - Vol. 7, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - Vol. 8, 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Vol. 9, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - Vol. 10, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Vol. 11, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Vol. 12, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Vol. 13, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Vol. 14, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - Vol. 15, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Vol. 16, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Vol. 17, 1997 (Box 22)
  - Vol. 18, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Vol. 19, 1994-1998. (Box 23)
    Materials related to publication of Karski - How One Man Tried to Stop Holocaust
  - Vol. 20, 1985-2000. (Box 23)
    Materials related to publication of The Great Powers, Emisariusz Witold, Misja Ostatniej Nadziei, Tajne Państwo
- Memorabilia, 1943-1991. (Box 23-24)
  Cigarette holder, drawing and medals
  - Drawing of Jan Karski by Feliks Topolski, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Cigarette holder. Personal gift from Prime Minister General Wladyslaw Sikorski with engraved inscription "Sikorski Gen. January 1943". Sterling silver (Box 24)
  - Polonia Restituta. Two medals (medal and medal with ribbon), lapel pin, certificate, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Raoul Wallenberg Medal, University of Michigan, 1991; Jan Karski's name engraved on metal plate (Box 24)
- Audio-Visual File, circa 1938-2007. (Box 25-35)
  Photographs, photo albums, videotapes, sound recordings, containing interviews, lectures, and personal testimonies.
  - Photographs, circa 1938-2000
    - Prints depicting private events with Jan Karski in attendance, 2000 (Folder 25: 1)
    - Prints depicting Jan Karski's family before 1939 (Folder 25: 2)
    - Print depicting Jan Karski in mid 1990s (Folder 25: 3)
    - Pola Nirenska's photo album with inscription, Dresden, 1930. Prints depicting Pola Nirenska after 1945 (Folder 25: 4)
    - Pola Nirenska's photo album depicting her and members of her family before 1939 (Folder 25: 5)
    - Jan Karski's photo album depicting his wedding in 1965 and Pola Nirenska's photo album depicting her life before 1939 (Folder 25: 6)
    - Prints depicting public events at Georgetown University with Jan Karski in attendance, 1980s (Folder 25: 7)
    - Prints depicting various stages of Jan Karski's life from 1941 to 1980s, Karski's visit to Holocaust Museum in Washington DC with Tom Wood, 1994 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Audio cassette tapes, 1986-1997; 87 tapes (Box 25-29)
    Interviews, lectures, personal testimonies. Includes Eyewitnesses to History, 1996. A partial list of sound recordings is provided below.
    - Sound recording of The Story Teller of Jerusalem by Abraham Cykiert, 1978 (Box 26)
      "Petition" (side A) is a story about leaving a note in a wall in Jerusalem and an encounter with the keeper of Jerusalem's soul. "Benjamin" (side B) concerns a woman's experiences with two children named Benjamin, in part overlapping the Six Days War. The cassette label contains a copyright notice. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002183
    - Sound recording of Larry King interview with Jan Karski, 1980 December 10 (Box 26)
      (Side B) Karski speaks about growing up in Poland, his experiences escaping from the Nazis during World War II and joining the Polish Underground, leaving Poland for asylum in America, and Poland during the Cold War. They spend a great amount of time discussing the current buildup of Soviet forces at the border of Poland. Karski believes the USSR will not go into Poland, but offers his analysis if such a thing should occur. Several of the call-in questions are about anti-Semitism in Poland. Recording includes all the commercials during the breaks. Some callers briefly speak Polish to Karski. Side A label reads: INTERVIEW WITH ANDRZEJ POMIAN for Radio Free Europe, 12/10/80. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002184
    - Sound recording of Professor Jan Karski Polska pomoc Zydom w czasie wojny, 1982 April 18 (Box 26)
      Prof. Jan Karski Polska pomoc Zydom w czasie wojny. Odczyt 18/4/1982 w Domu Polskim w San Francisco. Original shell side A label reads: Prof.dr Jan Karski / Polska pomoc Zydom w czasie wojny / odczyt 18:IV. 1982 w Domu Polskim w San Francisco Mowce wprowadzil prof.dr J. Lerski. Original shell side B label reads: c.d. odpowiedzi na pytania po od-czycie prof. Jana Karskiego. In Polish. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002344
    - Sound recording of Professor Engel interview of Jan Karski, 1982 April 18 (Box 26)
      Discussing Karski's experiences in the Polish underground; topics include analyzing the Jewish people in Poland and their relationship with the Soviet Union, and his meeting with Franklin Roosevelt. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002350
    - Sound recording of Wywiad dla radia "Nocne rodakow rozmowy", 1983 October 25; Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002354 (Box 26)
    - Days of Remembrance sound recording, 1984 May 1 (Box 26)
      A ceremony remembering the Holocaust. Jan Karski is among the speakers. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002454
    - Sound recording of interview z Ryszardem Mossin, Pazdziernik, 1984 (Box 26)
      Interview with Jan Karski in Polish. Also on the first tape is an American panel discussion about the 1984 U.S. presidential election, in English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002455
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski speech: My Jewish Mission, 1984 October 28 (Box 26)
      Karski speaks about his work in the Polish Underground in regards to Jews. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002456
    - Sound recording of Radio Free Europe Karski-Pomian interview, 1985 November 8 (Box 26)
      In Polish. Radio Free Europe, Karski-Pomian, Shoah, I-II, November 1985. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002495
    - The Unheeded Message of the Holocaust sound recording, 1986 (Box 26)
      With Professor Karski. Produced by the Australian Broadcasting Company. In English. Label reads: The Unheeded Message of the Holocaust Mo[???]: Andrew Philun. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002496
    - Rozmowa w pazdzierniku sound recording, 1986 (Box 26)
      In Polish. Jan Karski, Jagoda Jedrychowska. Side A label reads: Jan Karski [???] 1986. I. J. J[???]howska. Side B label reads: Jan Karski - Gazdn. 1986 I. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002497
    - Sound recording of Rozmowa w pazdzierniku (sound tape III), 1986 (Box 26)
      In Polish. Jan Karski, Jagoda Jedrychowska. Rozmowa w pazdzierniku, 1986. Tape III. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002498
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski on the Tim Coles Show, 1987 February 23 (Box 26)
      The discussion focuses on the World War II era and the Yalta Conference, particular the relationships between the US, UK, and USSR. In English. Side A label reads: WPLP AM57 News Talk Radio Jan Karsky on the Tim Coles Show 2/23/87. Side B label reads: St. Petersburg 813/541-6651 Tampa 813/221-0358. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002734
    - Sound recording of Radio Canada International interview with Jan Karski, 1987 March 20 (Box 27)
      In Polish. Recording date: March 20, 1987. Broadcast date: March 29, 1987. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002735
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski speech to the Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1987 March 29 (Box 27)
      In English. Label: An Eyewitness Report. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002736
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski speech: My Jewish Missions, 1942-1943, 1987 May 30 (Box 27)
      Chicago, Illinois. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002737
    - Jan Karski in Polish sound recording, 1987 May 30 (Box 27)
      Side 1 label reads: Mr. J. Karski in Polish. Side 2 label reads: Chicago, Ill. Moje Misje w Sprawie Zydow 1942 1943 Odoszt - 31 maja 1987. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002738
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski speech: Jewish Appeals for Help and Western Leaders Reaction, 1987 March 29 (Box 27)
      A talk by Karski concerning his actions with the Polish Underground during World War II and the aftermath. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002739
    - Sound recording of Interviews with radio SBS in Melbourne, 1993 November 6-7 (Box 27)
      In English and Polish. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002780
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski interview in Australia, 1993 November 8 (Box 27)
      Jan Karski interviewed in Australia. They discuss Karski's relationship with his past. Karski says he unwillingly came forward with his story, only after Elie Wiesel got him to. He says he tried to run from his memories for 30 years following the Holocaust. In English. Label reads: Doug Aiton with Prof Jan Karski. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002826
    - Katyn sound recordings from April 1988, 1988 April 15-22 (Box 27)
      In Polish. Katyn / Powstanie w getcie harszanskim. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002827
    - Sound recording of Local Considerations radio interview with Jan Karski, 1990 April 4 (Box 27)
      Describing international politics of Europe during World War II in regards to Allies' aid to Jews. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002828
    - Polish Panorama sound recording, 1991 January 20 (Box 27)
      Polish Panorama show. The lead is an interview with Jan Karski at his home about his work with the Polish underground. Topics include Karski's Jesuit background, his work with Western forces during the war, why Karski does not like the word "holocaust," Western response to the news of the Holocaust, how te Holocaust should be taught to children, the implications upon the nature of man, and the American Holocaust museum among other topics. The program continues after the interview. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002832
    - Sound recording of American-Jewish Committee annual dinner, 1993 May 6 (Box 27)
      Includes a speech by Attorney General Janet Reno speaking on crime in America. Jan Karski speaks in the second half discussing the Holocaust. He holds that another holocaust is not possible because of the existence of Israel. Following Karski, Bosnian Foreign Minister Haris Silajdžić speaks. Then, Israeli Ambassador Itamar Rabinovich speaks. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002833
    - Sound recording of Danielle Charak interview of Dr. Jan Karski for Radio Melbourne, 1993 November 7 (Box 27)
      In Yiddish and English. Label reads: Yiddish 7.11.93 9.15 am SBS Radio Melbourne Dr. Jan Karski - [??] Danielle Charak Australia. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002834
    - Jan Karski sound recording, 1994 May 10 (Box 27)
      Label reads: Jan Karski - Golan R[???] [???] May 10, 1994. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002835
    - Jan Karski Voice of America sound recording, 1994 August 27 (Box 27)
      Label reads: Karski-Wierzvnski V.O.A. August 27, 1994. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002836
    - Sound recording of Jan Karski interview on New York public radio, 1994 November 22 (Box 27)
      A discussion of Karski's experiences during World War II. Topics include: why Karski kept quiet following the war, films--propaganda and not--about the war, anti-Semitism in Europe before the war, people that helped Karski and how he got around Europe, and his meeting with dignitaries in the West. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002837
    - Sound recording of radio program, 1993 (Box 27)
      Noam Chomsky on the American intervention in Somalia. Label on the cassette concerns an interview Jan Karski gave to a Melbourne radio station, but the only interview on the tape is Noam Chomsky on Australian radio. In English. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002919
    - Sound recording of On the Mark radio interview with Jan Karski and Thomas Wood, 1994 October 26 (Box 27)
      Mark Gilman interviews Jan Karski and Thomas Wood. They discuss the writing process and stories of the book "Karski" as well as the implications for present society. Karski believes Wood knows more about Karski's actions during the war than Karski himself. Topics include: possibility of a future Holocaust, Karski's meeting with FDR, Holocaust deniers, remembering history, Karski's faith, Schindler's List, oversimplifying events and education, and the Holocaust Museum. In English. WAVA 105, Arlington, Virginia. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002920
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated; Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002921 (Box 27)
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 39.27/2. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0002922
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 40.27/3. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003082
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 41.27/4. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003083
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 42.27/5. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003084
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 43.27/6. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003085
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 44.27/7. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003086
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 45.27/8. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003087
    - Sound recording of interview with Jan Karski in Polish, undated (Box 28)
      Cassette 46.27/9. Likely to be a continuation of previous tape. Use copy reference number: 46033_a_0003354
    - Sound recording of Page One show 470, 1990 (Box 28)